http://www.paulfredrick.com/custservice/privacy.aspx

clearance big & tall
Up to 50% off Everything plus Two-Day Only Offers. Free Shipping on all orders.
Click to Activate
Select styles. Prices as marked. Cannot be combined with other offers. Free Shipping on all orders valid on ground shipping. Excludes prior sales, gift cards and clearance. Expires 12/11/2020.
Apply Promotion
More Details
h4pppb
Order Status
Call Us
800.247.1417
Search
Sign In
Safety/Privacy
Paul Fredrick is committed to respecting the privacy of our customers.
The information collected on our site is used to improve your shopping experience and communicate with you regarding Paul Fredrick products. We do not collect any of your personal information unless you provide it to us. The information collected includes your first and last name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card information. This information is used to process your order and contact you regarding your order, if necessary. Optional clothing and size preferences are also collected if provided by you. This information is used to contact you about Paul Fredrick products specific to your preferences.
We also work with several third-party vendors and their service providers for marketing and advertising purposes. These parties may collect and use site data;
however, they keep your personal information confidential throughout their processes. In some cases, the information we disclose may include your transactional
information with us. We do not allow such third parties to collect any credit card, user name or password information. To learn more about Internet-Based advertising
or to opt-out, click here and here.
We will not rent, sell or exchange your email address. A third party is used for email transmission. A blank image is used in individual html emails to track the open rates for email campaigns. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email newsletter at any time, click here.
You may receive a Paul Fredrick catalog if you provide a postal address. We occasionally make our customer names and postal addresses available to select firms. If you would prefer to not to receive such third-party mailings, please contact us by phone at 1-800-247-1417 or by email at custserv@paulfredrick.com.
If you have registered for a Paul Fredrick My Account, you have the ability to change, edit or delete your personal information online by signing in to your account on the sign in page. Please contact us by phone at 1-800-247-1417 or by email at custserv@paulfredrick.com. if you have any questions or need assistance with updating your personal information.
We utilize cookie technology in order to enhance your shopping experience. Cookies are used to assign you a unique and encrypted id when you visit PaulFredrick.com. This id is used if you return to PaulFredrick.com in order to determine if you have items not yet purchased from a previous shopping session stored in your shopping bag.
This website uses Mouseflow: a website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback campaigns,
and similar features/functionality. Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, form fills (keystrokes) in non-excluded fields,
pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type
(first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language, and similar meta data. Mouseflow does not collect
any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser. If you'd like to opt-out,
you can do so at https://mouseflow.com/opt-out.
If you'd like to obtain a copy of your data, make a correction, or have it erased, please contact
us first or, as a secondary option, contact Mouseflow at privacy@mouseflow.com.
For more information, see Mouseflow’s Privacy Policy at https://mouseflow.com/privacy/.
For more information on Mouseflow and GDPR, visit https://mouseflow.com/gdpr/.
For more intormation on Mouseflow and CCPA visit https://mouseflow.com/ccpa.
We partner with Rakuten Advertising, who may collect personal information when you interact with our site. The collection and
use of this information is subject to the privacy policy located here:
Rakuten’s privacy policy:
https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/
To submit an opt-out request: https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/subject-requests/
PaulFredrick.com may match user information with third party data for research purposes only. Also, we disclose aggregate user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, other third parties and for other lawful purposes.
PaulFredrick.com may disclose user information in order to identify, contact or bring legal action to person or persons causing injury or interference with the property or business practices of PaulFredrick.com or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We will disclose information in good faith when required to do so by law.
PaulFredrick.com is not liable or responsible for the independent practices and/or privacy policies of other sponsors, merchants, affiliates, advertisers or other persons in correlation with our website. PaulFredrick.com is not responsible for any email transmission problems that would prevent a customer from receiving an email from Paul Fredrick or if Paul Fredrick were not able to receive an email from a customer.
PaulFredrick.com may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted third party partners.
These partners may combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that PaulFredrick.com
may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail.
If you do not want PaulFredrick.com to collect information about you,
please contact PaulFredrick.com to opt out.
If any changes are made in the future to the Paul Fredrick Privacy Policy, the date the change was made and a brief description of the change will be listed on our privacy policy page.
If you are still concerned about your personal privacy, please email your question to custserv@paulfredrick.com. or call us at 1-800-247-1417.
Paul Fredrick Privacy Policy effective as of 4/6/2010.
Privacy Policy updated 4/6/2010. Third paragraph of privacy policy was added.
Privacy Policy updated 4/8/2011. ClickTale tracking was added to the Policy.
Device Usage Research
We participate in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op to understand how you use our website across different devices so that we can better tailor promotions to you.
Learn more about how Adobe’s program works and manage your preferences here.
Security
Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology is used by Paul Fredrick to encrypt your order information. This protects all of your information from being decoded by anyone other than Paul Fredrick. The secure mode begins when you start to check out on our website.
Paul Fredrick Guarantee
We GUARANTEE a perfect fit. If you are not completely satisfied, we want to make it right.
Exchanges are free within 90 days, domestic shipping fees waived.
Return it within 90 days and receive a prompt refund of the purchase price.
After 90 days, a merchandise credit for the lowest sales price within the last three months will be issued for any
item returned in original condition.
Custom dress shirts cannot be exchanged or returned.
Toll Free Fax: 1-800-713-3512.
By Phone / Fax outside the U.S. or Canada
Customer Service: 1-800-247-1417
Fax:
You may send an email to custserv@paulfredrick.com.
Receive Exclusive Offers
Sign up for our emails and you’ll be the first to know about new collections, products and offers.
Email Address
New Arrivals
Shop through our newest catalog online and see the latest products.
